Finding Aid for the Recordings of June in Buffalo, 1975-1978, 1980
State University of New York at Buffalo. Music Library
- Concert recordings, 1975-1978, 1980, I; Reel 1-2, 7-68
  - June in Buffalo Concert 20: Music of Erik Satie, June 16, 1976, 1 10-inch reel of audio tape; Transferred to CD 26. Preservation master on DVD 24. (Box 1, Reel 28)
    Work number: JIB20_001
    Satie, Erik, 1866-1925
    Trois morceaux en forme de poire (1903)
    Performers: Yvar Mikhashoff, Nils Vigeland, pianos
    Duration: 15:18
    Work number: JIB20_002
    Habit de cheval (1911)
    Duration: 6:25
    Work number: JIB20_003
    Trois nocturnes (1919)
    Performers: Nils Vigeland, piano
    Duration: 7:53
    Work number: JIB20_004
    Socrate (1918)
    Performers: Martha Hanneman, soprano; Nils Vigeland, piano
    Duration: 30:35
  - June in Buffalo Concert 21: Music of George Crumb, June 18, 1976, 1 10-inch reel of audio tape; Transferred to CD 27-28. Preservation master on DVD 25. (Box 1, Reel 29)
    Work number: JIB21_001
    Madrigals, book I
    Performers: Martha Hanneman, soprano; Donald Knaack, Jan Williams, percussion; Makoto Michii, double bass
    Duration: 10:39
    Work number: JIB21_002
    Madrigals, book II
    Performers: Martha Hanneman, soprano; Eberhard Blum, flute; Donald Knaack, Jan Williams, percussion
    Duration: 7:35
    Work number: JIB21_003
    Madrigals, book III
    Performers: Martha Hanneman, soprano; Suzanne Thomas, harp; Donald Knaack, Jan Williams, percussion
    Duration: 8:46
    Work number: JIB21_004
    Madrigals, book IV
    Performers: Martha Hanneman, soprano; Suzanne Thomas, harp; Eberhard Blum, flute; Donald Knaack, Jan Williams, percussion; Makoto Michii, double bass
    Duration: 11:57
    Work number: JIB21_005
    Music for a summer evening (Makrokosmos III, 1974)
    Performers: Yvar Mikhashoff, John Newell, pianos; John Boudler, Lynn Harbold, percussion
    Duration: 41:43
  - June in Buffalo Concert 22: Piano Music of Aaron Copland, June 1, 1977, 1 10-inch reel of audio tape; Transferred to CD 29-30. Preservation master on DVD 26. (Box 1, Reel 30)
    Work number: JIB22_001
    Copland, Aaron, 1900-1990
    Passacaglia (1922)
    Performers: Leo Smit, piano
    Duration: 6:31
    Work number: JIB22_002
    Piano variations (1930)
    Duration: 11:37
    Work number: JIB22_003
    Sonata, piano, 1939-41
    Duration: 22:42
    Work number: JIB22_004
    Scherzo humoristique, The cat and the mouse (1920)
    Duration: 3:26
    Work number: JIB22_005
    Four piano blues (1926-48)
    Duration: 7:52
    Work number: JIB22_006
    Night thoughts (1972)
    Duration: 7:33
    Work number: JIB22_007
    Piano fantasy (1955-57)
    Duration: 31:34
  - June in Buffalo Concert 23: Music of Farwell, Loeffler, Griffes, Beach, June 2, 1977, 1 10-inch reel of audio tape; Transferred to CD 31. Preservation master on DVD 27. (Box 1, Reel 31)
    Work number: JIB23_001
    Farwell, Arthur George, 1872-1952
    To Morfydd (1903)
    Performers: Nora Post, oboe; Yvar Mikhashoff, piano
    Duration: 3:20
    Work number: JIB23_002
    Loeffler, Charles Martin, 1861-1935
    Two rhapsodies for oboe, viola and piano (1905)
    Performers: Nora Post, oboe; Richard Field, viola; Yvar Mikhashoff, piano
    Duration: 21:33
    Work number: JIB23_003
    Griffes, Charles Tomlinson, 1884-1920
    Sonata, piano
    Duration: 12:34
    Work number: JIB23_004
    Quintet, piano-string
    Performers: Thomas Halpin, Marie Yadzinski, violins; Richard Field, viola; Frances-Marie Uitti, violoncello; Yvar Mikhashoff, piano
    Duration: 29:39
  - June in Buffalo Concert 24: Music of Terry Riley, June 3, 1977, 2 10-inch reels of audio tape; Transferred to CD 32-33. Preservation master on DVD 28. (Box 1, Reel 32-33)
    Preceded by audience noise and laughter (1:02).
    Work number: JIB24_001
    Riley, Terry, 1935-
    [Improvisation]
    Performers: Terry Riley, electric organ
    Duration: 40:15
    Work number: JIB24_002
    Duration: 42:08
  - June in Buffalo Concert 25: Music of Druckman, Wolpe, Babbitt, Bartok, June 7, 1977, 1 10-inch reel of audio tape; Transferred to CD 34-35. Preservation master on DVD 29. (Box 1, Reel 34)
    Work number: JIB25_001
    Druckman, Jacob, 1928-1996
    Quartet, strings, no. 2 (1966)
    Performers: Concord String Quartet: Mark Sokol, Andrew Jennings, violins; John Kochanowski, viola; Norman Fischer, violoncello
    Duration: 18:07
    Work number: JIB25_002
    Wolpe, Stefan
    Quartet, strings (1968-69)
    Duration: 18:59
    Work number: JIB25_003
    Babbitt, Milton, 1916-
    Quartet, strings, no. 2
    Duration: 14:25
    Work number: JIB25_004
    Bartók, Béla, 1881-1945
    Quartet, strings, no. 6 (1939)
    Duration: 34:13
  - June in Buffalo Concert 26: Piano music of Schoenberg, Webern, Berg, June 8, 1977, 1 10-inch reel of audio tape; Transferred to CD 36-37. Preservation master on DVD 30. (Box 1, Reel 35)
    Work number: JIB26_001
    Duration: 13:48
    Work number: JIB26_002
    Sechs kleine Klavierstücke, op. 19 (1911)
    Duration: 5:48
    Work number: JIB26_003
    Klavierstücke, op. post. (1925)
    Duration: 1:12
    Work number: JIB26_004
    Klavierstücke, op. 33b (1932)
    Duration: 3:14
    Work number: JIB26_005
    Berg, Alban, 1885-1935
    Sonata, piano, op. 1 (1908)
    Duration: 11:04
    Work number: JIB26_006
    Fünf Klavierstücke, op. 23 (1923)
    Duration: 11:03
    Work number: JIB26_007
    Duration: 5:46
    Work number: JIB26_008
    Klavierstücke, op. 33a (1932)
    Duration: 2:10
    Work number: JIB26_009
    Suite, op. 25 (1924)
    Duration: 16:04
  - June in Buffalo Concert 27: Percussion Music of Cowell, Cage, Harrison, June 9, 1977, 1 10-inch reel and 1 7-inch reel of audio tape; Transferred to CD 38. Preservation master on DVD 31. (Box 1, Reel 36-37)
    Work number: JIB27_001
    Cowell, Henry, 1897-1965
    Ostinato pianissimo (1941)
    Performers: Dan Mink, wood blocks; Michael Pugliese, gongs; Joanne Rosenberg, tom-toms; Charles Clifton, piano; Michael Friedland, piano; Gregory Ketchum, bongos; Albert Furness, rice bowls; Timothy Leaphart, xylophone solo; John Boudler, conductor
    Duration: 3:57
    Work number: JIB27_002
    Banshee (1925)
    Duration: 3:48
    Work number: JIB27_003
    Pulse (1939)
    Performers: Michael Pugliese, dragon's mouth, woodblocks; Albert Furness, tom-toms; Timothy Leaphart, rice bowls; John Boudler, temple gongs; Gregory Ketchum, cymbals, gongs; Dan Mink, pipes, brake drums; Jan Williams, conductor
    Duration: 4:16
    Work number: JIB27_004
    She is asleep (1943)
    Performers: John Boudler, Gregory Ketchum, Timothy Leaphart, Michael Pugliese, tom-toms
    Duration: 4:02
    Work number: JIB27_005
    Amores (1943)
    Performers: John Boudler, Gregory Ketchum, Albert Furness, tom-toms, woodblocks, pod rattle; Yvar Mikhashoff, prepared piano
    Duration: 10:08
    Work number: JIB27_006
    Imaginary landscape, no. 3 (1942)
    Performers: Albert Furness, audio frequency oscillator; John Boudler, tin cans; Timothy Leaphart, tin cans; Dan Mink, buzzer, variable frequency oscillator; Gregory Ketchum, muted gongs, generator whine; Michael Pugliese, amplified slinky, marimbula; Walter Gajewski, electronics; Jan Williams, conductor
    Duration: 3:50
    Work number: JIB27_007
    Harrison, Lou, 1917-2003
    Song of Queztecoatl (1941)
    Performers: John Boudler, bowls, dragon's mouths, woodblocks, maracas, sistrum; Albert Furness, brake drums, cowbells, rattle; Timothy Leaphart, snare drum, guiro, windglass, triangle, gong, tam-tam; Michael Pugliese, tom-toms, bass drum
    Duration: 6:06
    The following is preceded by a partial recording of the work (6:35).
    Work number: JIB27_008
    Suite (1942)
    Performers: Gregory Ketchum, brake drums, triangles, dragon's mouths; John Boudler, brake drums, small bells; Dan Mink, brake drum, clock coils; Timothy Leaphart, washtub, thundersheet; Albert Furness, tam-tam, gongs, bass drum; Jan Williams, conductor
    Duration: 9:10
  - June in Buffalo Concert 28: Music of Milton Babbitt, June 10, 1977, 1 10-inch reel of audio tape; Transferred to CD 39-40. Preservation master on DVD 32. (Box 1, Reel 38)
    Introductory remarks to the first work by Milton Babbitt are on a separate track, with additional remarks preceding each of the other works. Comments introducing the second work are on the end of the first track, the comments introducing the third work are on the end of the second track, the comments introducing the fourth work are on a separate track, and comments introducing the fifth work are on the end of the fourth track.
    Work number: JIB28_001
    Ensembles for synthesizer (1962-64)
    Performers: Tape played
    Duration: 10:00
    Work number: JIB28_002
    Composition for four instruments (1947-48)
    Performers: Henrik Svitzer, flute; Edward Yadzinski, clarinet; Marie Yadzinski, violin; Don Reinfeld, violoncello
    Work number: JIB28_003
    Partitions for piano (1957)
    Performed twice.
    Duration: 5:13 (one performance)
    Work number: JIB28_004
    Quartet, winds (1953)
    Performers: Henrik Svitzer, flute; Nora Post, oboe; Edward Yadzinski, clarinet; Darlene Reynard, bassoon
    Duration: 11:24
    Work number: JIB28_005
    Occasional variations for synthesizer (1971)
    Duration: 10:59
  - June in Buffalo Concert 29: Music of Lukas Foss, June 14, 1977, 2 10-inch reels of audio tape; Transferred to CD 41-43. Preservation master on DVD 33. (Box 2, Reel 39-40)
    Work number: JIB29_001
    Foss, Lukas, 1922-2009
    Paradigm (1970)
    Performers: Jan Williams, percussion; Nora Post, oboe; Don Reinfeld, violoncello; Edward Yadzinski, clarinet, bass clarinet; Stu Weissman, electric guitar; Jan Williams, conductor
    Duration: 25:46
    Work number: JIB29_002
    Map (1970) (1977 version)
    Performers: James Kasprowicz, brass; Don Reinfeld, strings; Jan Williams, percussion; Edward Yadzinski, winds; Walter Gajewski, electronics
    Duration: 1:20:05 (divided between two CDs)
  - June in Buffalo Concert 30: Music of Nemiroff, Wolpe, June 15, 1977, 1 10-inch reel of audio tape; Transferred to CD 44-45. Preservation master on DVD 34. (Box 2, Reel 41)
    Introductory remarks about Stefan Wolpe by Morton Feldman (8:19).
    Work number: JIB30_001
    Nemiroff, Isaac
    Duo for oboe and bass clarinet
    Performers: Nora Post, oboe; Jack Kreiselman, bass clarinet
    Duration: 7:26
    Work number: JIB30_002
    Form (1959)
    Performers: Anne Chamberlain, piano
    Duration: 3:32
    Work number: JIB30_003
    Form IV. Broken sequences (1969)
    Duration: 4:12
    Work number: JIB30_004
    Sonata, oboe, piano, 1939-41
    Performers: Nora Post, oboe; Anne Chamberlain, piano
    Duration: 19:37
    Work number: JIB30_005
    Four Palestinian songs: Two songs from the Song of Solomon --If it be my fate -- Epitaph.
    Performers: Suze Leal, mezzo-soprano; Yvar Mikhashoff, piano
    Duration: 16:22
    Work number: JIB30_006
    Suite in hexachord for oboe and clarinet (1936)
    Performers: Nora Post, oboe; Jack Kreiselman, clarinet
    Duration: 14:46
  - June in Buffalo Concert 31: Music of Lejaren Hiller, June 16, 1977, 1 10-inch reel of audio tape; Transferred to CD 46. Preservation master on DVD 35. (Box 2, Reel 42)
    Introductory remarks, largely about sonata form, by Lejaren Hiller (11:23).
    Work number: JIB31_001
    Sonata, violin, piano, no. 2, 1955
    Performers: Thomas Halpin, violin; Yvar Mikhashoff, piano
    Duration: 16:37
    Work number: JIB31_002
    Machine music (1964)
    Performers: John Boudler, percussion; Yvar Mikhashoff, piano; Ralph Jones, electronic tape
    Duration: 15:06
    Concert concluded with tape played of Hiller's Electronic sonata for four-channel tape, which was not recorded as part of the concert. It was the premiere performance.
  - June in Buffalo Concert 32: Music of Jacob Druckman, June 17, 1977, 1 10-inch reel of audio tape; Transferred to CD 47. Preservation master on DVD 36. (Box 2, Reel 43)
    Introductory remarks by Jacob Druckman (17:32).
    Work number: JIB32_001
    Animus I
    Performers: James Kasprowicz, trombone
    Duration: 13:16
    Work number: JIB32_002
    Animus II
    Performers: Joan Collopy, soprano; Jan Williams, John Boudler, percussion
    Duration: 23:03
  - June in Buffalo Concert 33: String quartets of Elliott Carter, June 1, 1978, 2 10-inch reels of audio tape; Transferred to CD 48-49. Preservation master on DVD 37. (Box 2, Reel 44-45)
    Work number: JIB33_001
    Carter, Elliott, 1908-
    Quartet, strings, no. 2 (1959)
    Performers: Composers' Quartet: Matthew Raimondi, Anahid Ajemian, violins; Jean Dane, viola; Mark Shuman, violoncello
    Duration: 19:34
    Work number: JIB33_002
    Quartet, strings, no. 3 (1973)
    Duration: 20:43
    Work number: JIB33_003
    Quartet, strings, no.1 (1951)
    Duration: 38:20
  - June in Buffalo Concert 35: Music of Henry Brant, June 6, 1978, 2 10-inch reels of audio tape; Transferred to CD 50-51. Preservation master on DVD 38. (Box 2, Reel 46-47)
    Introductory remarks by Henry Brant (2:19).
    Work number: JIB35_001
    Brant, Henry, 1913-2008
    Ice age (1954)
    Performers: Yvar Mikhashoff, piano; Gary Hatt, clarinet; Henry Brant, Gregory Ketchum, percussion; Sylvia Brigham-Dimiziani, soprano
    Duration: 7:21
    Work number: JIB35_002
    Encephalograms 2 (1955)
    Performers: Sylvia Brigham-Dimiziani, soprano; Robert Dick, piccolo; Gary Hatt, clarinet; Nora Post, oboe; Yvar Mikhashoff, piano; Mario Falcao, harp; Gregory Ketchum, percussion; Michael Burke, organ
    Duration: 6:44
    Work number: JIB35_003
    Piri (1954)
    Performers: Robert Dick, flute; Mario Falcao, harp; Yvar Mikhashoff, piano; Jan Williams, glockenspiel
    Duration: 4:10
    Work number: JIB35_004
    Hieroglyphics (1966)
    Performers: Weronika Knittel, solo violin; Mario Falcao, harp; Krzysztof Knittel, celeste; Michael Pugliese, percussion; Sylvia Brigham-Dimiziani, voice; Henry Brant, organ
    Duration: 15:22
    Introductory remarks about the work Headhunt by Henry Brant (4:14).
    Work number: JIB35_005
    Headhunt (1962)
    Performers: James Kasprowicz, trombone; Gary Haft, clarinet; Michael Peebles, violoncello; Darlene Reynard, bassoon; Henry Brant, Gregory Ketchum, percussion
    Duration: 16:10
    Work number: JIB35_006
    Prevailing winds (1974)
    Performers: Robert Dick, flute; Nora Post, oboe; Gary Hatt, clarinet; Darlene Reynard, bassoon; Lowell Shaw, horn; Henry Brant, organ
    Duration: 19:09
  - June in Buffalo Concert 36: Music of Wolff, Rzewski, Wuorinen, June 7, 1978, 2 10-inch reels of audio tape; Transferred to CD 52-53. Preservation master on DVD 39. (Box 2, Reel 48-49)
    Work number: JIB36_001
    Bread and roses (1976)
    Performers: Ursula Oppens, piano
    Duration: 9:06
    Work number: JIB36_002
    Rzewski, Frederic
    Four pieces (1977)
    Duration: 32:22
    Work number: JIB36_003
    Wuorinen, Charles
    Duration: 32:01
  - June in Buffalo Concert 37: Lecture by Ben Johnston, "The Music of Harry Partch", June 8, 1978, 1 10-inch reel of audio tape; Transferred to CD 54-55. Preservation master on DVD 40. (Box 2, Reel 50)
    Work number: JIB37_001
    Johnston, Ben
    Lecture: The music of Harry Partch
    Ben Johnston, lecturer
    Duration: 58:43
    Followed by questions and discussion (33:44).
  - June in Buffalo Concert 38: Music of Charles Wuorinen, June 9, 1978, 1 10-inch reel of audio tape; Transferred to CD 56. Preservation master on DVD 41. (Box 2, Reel 51)
    Introductory remarks by Charles Wuorinen (limited to change in order of works on program) (2:16).
    Work number: JIB38_001
    Fantasy for violin and piano (1974)
    Performers: Benjamin Hudson, violin; Charles Wuorinen, piano
    Duration: 15:44
    Work number: JIB38_002
    Violin variations (1972)
    Duration: 13:07
    Work number: JIB38_003
    The long and the short (1969)
    Duration: 9:25
    Work number: JIB38_004
    Six pieces for violin and piano (1977)
    Duration: 20:25
  - June in Buffalo Concert 39: Music of Lou Harrison and John Cage, June 12, 1978, 1 10-inch reel of audio tape; Transferred to CD 57. Preservation master on DVD 42. (Box 2, Reel 52)
    Work number: JIB39_001
    Performers: Albert Furness, Gregory Ketchum, Robert Mahoney, Michael Pugliese, percussion
    Duration: 6:03
    Work number: JIB39_002
    Fugue(1942)
    Duration: 4:08
    Work number: JIB39_003
    Duration: 9:26
    Work number: JIB39_004
    Cage, John and Harrison, Lou
    Double music (1941)
    Duration: 6:22
    Work number: JIB39_005
    Spontaneous earth (1944)
    Performers: Yvar Mikhashoff, prepared piano
    Duration: 2:23
    Work number: JIB39_006
    In the name of the Holocaust (1942)
    Work number: JIB39_007
    Primitive (1942)
    Duration: 3:40
    Work number: JIB39_008
    Duration: 4:34
    Work number: JIB39_009
    Duration: 13:06
  - June in Buffalo Concert 40: Music of Virgil Thomson, June 13, 1978, 1 10-inch reel of audio tape; Transferred to CD 58. Preservation master on DVD 43. (Box 2, Reel 53)
    Work number: JIB40_001
    Thomson, Virgil, 1896-1989
    Concerto for flute, strings and percussion (1954); arr.
    Performers: Robert Dick, flute; Yvar Mikhashoff, piano
    Duration: 12:00
    Work number: JIB40_002
    Sonata da chiesa (1926)
    Performers: Gary Hatt, clarinet; David Kuehn, trumpet; Richard Field, viola; Duane Saetveit, horn; James Kasprowicz, trombone; Jan Williams, conductor
    Duration: 19:10
    Program concluded with a showing of the film Louisiana story (1948) with a soundtrack by Virgil Thomson. It was not recorded as part of the concert.
  - June in Buffalo Concert 41: String quartets of Charles Wuorinen, June 2, 1980, 1 10-inch reel of audio tape; Transferred to CD 59. Preservation master on DVD 44. (Box 2, Reel 54)
    Work number: JIB41_001
    Quartet, strings, no. 1 (1971)
    Performers: Benjamin Hudson, Carol Zeavin, violins; Janet Lyman Hill, viola; Andre Emelianoff, violoncello
    Duration: 24:28
    Work number: JIB41_002
    Quartet, strings, no. 2 (1979)
    Duration: 23:59
  - June in Buffalo Concert 42: String Quartet, 1979 by Morton Feldman, June 3, 1980, 1 10-inch reel of audio tape; Transferred to CD 60-61. Preservation master on DVD 45. (Box 2, Reel 55)
    Work number: JIB42_001
    Quartet, strings (1979)
    Duration: 1:43:37 (divided over 2 CDs)
  - June in Buffalo Concert 43: Music of Steve Reich, June 4, 1980, 1 10-inch reel of audio tape; Transferred to CD 62. Preservation master on DVD 46. (Box 2, Reel 56)
    Work number: JIB43_001
    Violin phase (1967)
    Performers: Shem Guibbory, violin
    Duration: 15:56
    Tape played at concert of Reich's Music for a large ensemble (1979), not recorded as part of the concert.
    Work number: JIB43_003
    My name is (1967-80)
    Performers:
    Duration: 17:15
    Work number: JIB43_004
    Octet (1979)
    Performers: Virgil Blackwell, Mort Silver, flutes, clarinets; Robert Chausow, Shem Guibbory, violins; Ruth Siegler, viola; Chris Finckel, violoncello; Edmund Niemann, Nurit Tilles, pianos
    Duration: 19:01
  - June in Buffalo Concert 44: Piano Music by Japanese composers, June 5, 1980, 1 10-inch reel of audio tape; Transferred to CD 63-64. Preservation master on DVD 47. (Box 2, Reel 57)
    Work number: JIB44_001
    Kai, Sesshu
    Music for piano I (1974)
    Performers: Aki Takahashi, piano
    Duration: 7:51
    Work number: JIB44_002
    Kondo, Jo, 1947-
    Sight rhythmics (1975)
    Duration: 11:31
    Work number: JIB44_003
    Takemitsu, Toru
    Les yeux clos (1979)
    Duration: 7:02
    Work number: JIB44_004
    Ichiyanagi, Toshi, 1933-
    Piano media (1972)
    Duration: 6:24
    Work number: JIB44_005
    Yuasa, Joji
    On the keyboard (1972)
    Duration: 5:45
    Work number: JIB44_006
    Takahashi, Yuji, 1938-
    Three poems of Mao Tse-Tung (1975)
    Duration: 11:44
    Work number: JIB44_007
    Satoh, Somei, 1947-
    Incarnation II (1978)
    Duration: 12:41
  - June in Buffalo Concert 45: Music of Arnold Schoenberg, June 6, 1980, 1 10-inch reel of audio tape; Transferred to CD 65. Preservation master on DVD 48. (Box 2, Reel 58)
    Work number: JIB45_001
    Gedichte aus Das Buch der hängenden Gärten (1908-09)
    Performers: Roswitha Trexler, soprano; Yvar Mikhashoff, piano
    Duration: 25:57
    Work number: JIB45_002
    Vier deutsche Volkslieder (1929)
    Duration: 10:09
    Work number: JIB45_003
    Haringer-Lieder, op. 48 (1933)
    Duration: 4:55
    Work number: JIB45_004
    Brettllieder (1901)
    Duration: 11:12
  - June in Buffalo Concert 46: Music of Won, Cage, Jolas, Amy, June 7, 1980, 1 10-inch reel of audio tape; Transferred to CD 66. Preservation master on DVD 49. (Box 2, Reel 59)
    Work number: JIB46_001
    Won, Yong Sook
    Nirvana (1979)
    Duration: 10:57
    Work number: JIB46_002
    Furniture music, Etcetera (1980)
    Performers: Aki Takahashi, Yvar Mikhashoff, pianos
    Duration: 19:49
    Composed for Aki Takahashi and Yvar Mikhashoff.
    Work number: JIB46_003
    Jolas, Betsy
    B for sonata (1979)
    Duration: 16:14
    Work number: JIB46_004
    Amy, Gilbert
    Inventions (1962)
    Performers: Robert Dick, flute; Mario Falcao, harp; Yvar Mikhashoff, piano; Bruce Penner, percussion
    Duration: 17:41
  - June in Buffalo Concert 47: Music of Nils Vigeland, June 8, 1980, 1 10-inch reel of audio tape; Transferred to CD 67. Preservation master on DVD 50. (Box 2, Reel 60)
    Work number: JIB47_001
    Vigeland, Nils
    Octet (1978)
    Performers: Marie Yadzinski, Susan Harbison, violins; Diane Williams, viola; Mary Sue Wells, violoncello; Nils Vigeland, piano; Edward Yadzinski, clarinet; Bruce Penner, percussion; Jan Williams, conductor
    Duration: 17:02
    Work number: JIB47_002
    Vara (1979)
    Performers: Edward Folger, David Gordon, Joel Harrod, Walter Hunt, Rick Kazmierczak, Bruce Penner, percussion; Nils Vigeland, piano; Jan Williams, conductor
    Duration: 25:42
    Work number: JIB47_003
    Sonata, piano, no. 1 (1979)
    Duration: 11:43
  - June in Buffalo Concert 48: Music by East German composers, June 9, 1980, 1 10-inch reel of audio tape; Transferred to CD 68. Preservation master on DVD 51. (Box 2, Reel 61)
    Work number: JIB48_001
    Dessau, Paul, 1894-1979
    Shakespeare-sonette (1971-74)
    Performers: Roswitha Trexler, soprano; Thomas Halpin, violin; Ronald Richards, oboe; Erik Skjoldan, piano; David Gibson, violoncello; James Kasprowicz, trombone; Jan Williams, conductor
    Duration: 11:36
    Work number: JIB48_002
    Voigtländer, Lothar, 1943-
    Drei elektronische Studien nach Texten von Erich Arendt fur Gesang, Klavier und Tonband (1976)
    Performers: Roswitha Trexler, soprano; Fritz Hennenberg, piano
    Duration: 10:01
    Tape realized by the composer.
    Work number: JIB48_003
    Schenker, Friedrich
    Versuch über Roswitha für Stimme und Tonband (1974)
    Performers: Roswitha Trexler, soprano
    Duration: 8:45
    Work number: JIB48_004
    Dittrich, Paul Heinz
    Kammermusik IV (1977)
    Performers: Roswitha Trexler, soprano; Scott Tinney, piano; Thomas Halpin, violin; David Gibson, violoncello; Robert Dick, flute; Ronald Richards, oboe; Edward Yadzinski, clarinet, bass clarinet; Michael Zak, electronics; Michael Andriaccio, guitar; Bruce Penner, percussion
    Duration: 26:31
  - June in Buffalo Concert 49: Music of Ralph Shapey, June 10, 1980, 1 10-inch reel of audio tape; Transferred to CD 69-70. Preservation master on DVD 52. (Box 2, Reel 62)
    Work number: JIB49_001
    Shapey, Ralph, 1921-2002
    Seven (1963)
    Performers: Frieda Manes, Stephen Manes, piano
    Duration: 7:29
    Work number: JIB49_002
    Configurations (1965)
    Performers: Robert Dick, flute; Aki Takahashi, piano
    Work number: JIB49_003